{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Gianluigi5.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "provare",
            "failed": 10,
            "lastAsked": 1488825414.484749,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to try\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to succeed",
            "failed": 12,
            "lastAsked": 1488825450.715663,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"riuscire\"?",
            "tried": 15
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "abbinare",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1488825447.1633537,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to match\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "stufarsi",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1488825365.1649675,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get tired with\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ripassare",
            "failed": 10,
            "lastAsked": 1488825443.0395293,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to review\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to get tired of"
            ],
            "answer": "to get tired with",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1488825361.6851327,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"stufarsi\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "incoraggiare",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1488825374.2248235,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to encourage\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere molto da fare",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1488825402.3484683,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to have a lot to do\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "allora",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1488825533.8577251,
            "question": "Given the definition \"therefore, well\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'insegnante",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1488825479.3068433,
            "question": "Given the definition \"teacher, instructor\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "riuscire",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1488825530.9457755,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to succeed\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "now",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1488825526.6337838,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"adesso\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cosi",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1488825499.8024135,
            "question": "Given the definition \"so\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la pazienza",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1488825504.2702727,
            "question": "Given the definition \"patience\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "encourage"
            ],
            "answer": "to encourage",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1488825486.8108125,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"incoraggiare\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "divertirsi",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1488825524.378267,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to have fun\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "invece"
            ],
            "answer": "invece di",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1488825586.105068,
            "question": "Given the definition \"instead\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere voglia di",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1488825635.0726154,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to feel like\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to review",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1488825562.4373233,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ripassare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il lavoro",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1488825640.4239058,
            "question": "Given the definition \"work, job\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "recitare",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1488825620.184643,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to recite\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "only",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1488825556.1895053,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"soltanto\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to feel like",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1488825628.8082757,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere voglia di\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "parola"
            ],
            "answer": "la parola",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1488825597.2206423,
            "question": "Given the definition \"word\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "calm, tranquil",
                "calm, tranquil, quiet"
            ],
            "answer": "quietness, calm",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1488825679.9513507,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la calma\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "capire"
            ],
            "answer": "capire(isc)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1488825655.4959373,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to understand\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fare colazione",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1488825646.3277905,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to have breakfast\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "patience",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1488825666.6395426,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la pazienza\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to try",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1488825663.1115623,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"provare\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to match",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1488825709.342799,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"abbinare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "therefore"
            ],
            "answer": "therefore, well",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1488825659.8640797,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"allora\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "soltanto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1488825711.9189131,
            "question": "Given the definition \"only\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to have fun",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1488825747.9943142,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"divertirsi\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to have much to do"
            ],
            "answer": "to have a lot to do",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1488825719.7823954,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere molto da fare\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "qualche volta",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1488825752.8022459,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sometimes\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to recite",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1488825745.1866658,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"recitare\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "so",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1488825749.682189,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"cosi\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la calma",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1488825714.7506409,
            "question": "Given the definition \"quietness, calm\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "adesso",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1488825729.0025015,
            "question": "Given the definition \"now\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "instead of"
            ],
            "answer": "instead",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1488825732.3586042,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"invece di\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "teacher"
            ],
            "answer": "teacher, instructor",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1488825761.6783903,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'insegnante\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sometimes",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1488825772.285699,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"qualche volta\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to understand",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1488825756.8220305,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"capire(isc)\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "word",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1488825766.8017418,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la parola\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "have breakfast"
            ],
            "answer": "to have breakfast",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1488825769.9376657,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fare colazione\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "job"
            ],
            "answer": "work, job",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1488825763.8818018,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il lavoro\"?",
            "tried": 3
        }
    ]
}